Christopher, Shin. Make your report.
Yes, ma'am.
You've got it.
But, well, it's exactly as you said.
The dragons are behaving strangely.
There was no activity
until this morning, but, well...
They don't seem to be out for blood.
We got fairly close to them,
but there was no indication they'd
immediately attack if a signal was given.
We thought the same thing!
It's like they're preoccupied.
It was like a funeral!
What's wrong with the superior dragons?
In all likelihood, they're somewhere else.
Actually, there's no definite proof
that filth was telling the truth.
I'm not sure why they're acting this way,
but this is a good opportunity.
A good opportunity?
The dragons certainly do not want
to let us off the hook.
If that was the case,
they would have raised their siege.
Uh-huh.
Some issue must have cropped up
for the superior dragons
that temporarily takes priority over us.
This is what I must assume.
It's utterly insulting.
But it's an insult to be thankful for.
Majorca.
Yes, ma'am!
How much longer will the
teleportation circle take to prepare?
Thaumaturge
Majorca Abbott
Ah! Yes, Your Highness!
Um, Fu said it'll take one day
if we work ourselves to death,
so it'll take two days to complete,
Your Highness!
Princess Lia addressed me! With words!
Tell Fu to get it done in one day
without anyone dying.
Being this close to the princess and breathing
the same air as her fills me with ecstasy!
Our country has already lost.
On the first night, five cities
and the capital fell.
I cannot fathom just how many citizens
have been devoured by dragons.
The only thing we can do is flee the country
with only the fifteen hundred citizens
we've gathered here.
It is entirely disgraceful.
But we shall escape!
We'll show those loathsome dragons
they can't always have their way with us!
We will survive!
Our people, the corps,
and every single one of you!
That was fantastic!
I expected nothing less from
the renowned Silverware Princess.
Even your excuses for turning tail
were dripping with charisma.
Just who the hell are you?
Knock it off, you two!
So you decided to make an appearance, filth.
I was going to pretend
I never saw you for a while,
but you just had to show up!
You bastard! What did you do
to the commander?
Hold up, hold up!
We already discussed this!
Episode 10: Stakes and Cooperation
I told you to behave yourselves!
This guy doesn't feel strong in the slightest!
Hey, Hesela. Do you think
one of those two might be him?
Totally, Greya! It must be one of them!
This is an incredibly skilled group.
There are even people who are
stronger than Leo here.
But...
What happened to the guards?
I asked them to let us through,
and they very kindly obliged.
What?
We'd like to lend you a hand
in your escape plan.
I got the gist of your plan.
You want to use dragon's blood
as a magical energy source
and teleport out of the country.
Am I correct?
I think that's a solid plan.
But it won't be successful.
The reason is simple.
The difference in military power between
you and your adversary is too great.
If you allow us to work together with you,
I will give you detailed intel
about the enemy.
Better yet,
I can provide you a superweapon capable of
slaying superior dragons unassisted.
Ragna the Reaper.
We must cooperate to take down the
two superior dragons who are our enemies.
If we don't...
We'll all die here together.
So his name is Ragna!
You'd like...
to help?
Princess...
Major, give us an explanation!
It's written all over her face!
Don't talk all at once!
I can't understand a thing you're saying!
What should I do?
Her Highness is losing it again!
You want to... help?
What sort of drivel is that, filth?
You're a stain that just can't be scrubbed
from the toilet bowl of this world!
It's impossible for us to cooperate.
I know this.
You don't play well with others.
You merely use others and get them killed.
This isn't your style, Commander.
Just get straight to the point,
like you usually do.
Do we kill him? Or not?
Hold on there.
It's my job to kill him.
We won't work with you!
Go back to your cell!
The next time I see your face, I'll kill you!
Y-you too, over there!
The Mad Maestro, Olto Zora.
The Sixth Seat of the Blood of the Wing.
His primary role is managing
and leading military matters.
His power is Chemical Synthesis.
He can make potent drugs
that instantly kill living beings
and drugs that hypnotize his targets.
He can alter his blood to create
a vast array of compounds
and can spray them over
a wide area as a mist.
But these chemicals are instantly
rendered ineffective in sunlight,
and silverine can stop them.
Having that information should
allow you to combat against them.
If anything, it's more of a nuisance
when he uses chemicals on his own forces.
Thanks to the chemicals, his dragon army's
power will be multiplied several times over,
and he'll have complete and utter control
over his hypnotized forces.
Of course, since he's a superior dragon,
his own power is tremendous.
Where'd he get this intel?
I've never heard such detailed information
about superior dragons.
What guarantee do we have
that your information is true?
If I was lying, you'd be able to tell,
wouldn't you?
Your very existence is so fishy,
I don't know if you're
telling the truth or not!
So it doesn't matter what I say?
Such a windbag!
Then let's tag in another player.
Hwah!
Hwah?
Go on, persuade the Silverware Princess.
There's no way I can do that!
That's more up your alley.
Me and that woman are totally incompatible.
But...
It'll be fine.
You could probably spew utter garbage,
and her fondness for you would only grow.
That can't be true.
You've made up your mind, right?
You're going to stay here and fight.
Not long from now,
I estimate that the number of dragons
attacking this base will be
at least ten thousand.
Nine thousand inferior dragons.
A thousand medial dragons.
About forty to fifty will be mature dragons.
They also have a mobile front to
transport them, the Writhing Shade.
There's a high probability the
Thirteenth Seat has been mobilized too.
Two superior dragons will lead them:
Olto Zora and Taratectra.
Their military force will be total overkill.
There are 350 soldiers here, as well as
1,500 civilians under their protection.
None will survive.
Were the Silverware Princess
and her comrades in your future?
This is my proposal.
If you promise to follow my orders
and give up on Ultimatia for a short while
so we can escape the country,
I'll use the full extent of my powers
to make sure the humans at this base
escape the dragons.
And when I say the full extent of my powers,
that's including you.
Break it off with me and go back
to the capital by yourself.
Or stay and fight to protect the people here,
then flee the country together.
What will you decide?
Miss Silverware Princess.
Wh-wh-wh-what? I won't work with you!
D-don't think that just because you're
kind of a looker that I'll listen to you!
Earlier...
D-don't think that just because you're
kind of a looker that I'll listen to you!
You called him a stain that just can't be
scrubbed from the toilet bowl of this world.
That's actually very accurate, I think.
What?
He's a despicable person.
He loves tormenting others
and gets kicks from it.
Honestly, he's kind of a piece of shit.
A piece of shit!
I often wonder why a guy like him
was even born.
I always think about how everyone would be
better off if I could just kill him already.
But the one thing you can trust about him
is his desire to kill dragons!
That's why I joined forces with him.
I decided that the two of us are going to
exterminate dragonkind together as a team!
Exterminate... all the dragons?
Hunting dragons is my forte!
I'm better at it than
anyone else in the world!
Use me, Silverware Princess!
I promise I can help you!
Huh? What's with that facial expression?
Did I make her mad?
The man she fell in love with at first sight
is ardently pleading her to use him.
And she is just barely resisting
screaming, "Yes!"
However...
You must not agree, Princess Lia!
That man is undoubtably a pervert!
He's the kind of degenerate who puts up
photos of his crush all over his bedroom!
I know he does! I can always
sniff out other freaks like me!
I know for a fact he's depraved!
But Ragna is her first love.
She doesn't know how to act around him.
And she can't allow herself to look like
a pathetic simp in front of the corps.
Thus, consequently...
Very well. I accept your proposal.
But do not be mistaken!
I'm temporarily borrowing your power
for strategic purposes and nothing more!
I d-d-didn't make this decision because of
any personal feelings I have for you!
Do not be mistaken!
That was like a bad tsundere impression.
What's so funny, filth!
Sorry!
That really tickled my funny bone!
Nice play.
I'm not a fan of being called
a piece of shit,
but I'll let it slide since the
Silverware Princess had me in stitches.
You told me to do it.
I didn't tell you to call me a piece of shit.
Is this a positive thing?
Well, it's better than them
being outright hostile.
But still... I just don't understand!
Are you serious, Commander?
I'm very serious!
What about my fight with them?
That will have to be postponed!
A most excellent decision,
Silverware Princess!
We'll certainly pulverize those vile dragons
with our combined forces.
First, let's modify the plan
based on my intel-
You'll cough up the information
about the dragons, and that's it.
I will be the one doing the planning.
That sure takes a load off my shoulders!
Just please do make sure
your plan has no holes.
It'd be a pain for me to have to
patch them later.
Hmph!
Then riddle me this.
A few hours ago, something about
the dragons sieging us changed.
If you know what happened to them, tell us.
Ah, yes!
That's because we fought against
the Winged Monarch in the capital.
What?
They're probably going into a frenzy
and rushing off to the capital
right about now.
Why do we even keep you around,
you senile old man!
I have no excuse I can give you.
Where is the progenitor now?
The progenitor is...
Why is this happening?
So you've lost control of time, huh?
I've said it before.
Ultimate power that you get from
someone else is fickle.
Why are you here?
I told Nebulim not to let anyone enter!
He let me waltz right in.
That can't be true!
You clearly must have threatened him
and forced your way in!
Leave at once! I'm not in the mood
to chitchat with you n-
Got you a souvenir.
Wh-who is that?
Hey, c'mon now. Did you actually forget
what you sent your errand boy to do?
This is the person who killed Trois?
Not convinced?
You don't think a lowly hunter
could've killed that dumb windbag, huh?
Well, this guy was at the bottom of
the barrel when it came to strength,
but he had a good death.
Guess what he said right before he croaked?
I don't want to hear it!
Finding amusement in the
last words of someone
who suffered while dying
is in such poor taste!
If you say so.
But to me, pretty much everyone else
in the world is insignificant trash.
I haven't faced many opponents
who wowed me.
And what was this guy's attitude
when he looked death in the eyes?
He was a weakling, yeah.
But he was a dragon hunter to the core.
But if you ain't interested, so be it.
I'll just keep his last words
between me and him.
Then how 'bout this?
One of the dragon hunters
I dealt with had it.
The craftsmanship is crude for a sword,
but the amount of silverine infused in it
and its chilling power is bananas.
Even I have to grip it with everything
I've got or my hand gets numb.
P-please get that thing away from me!
Don't be all shook up by it. Look, see!
St-stop it!
No! Seriously!
I said stop it!
What are you playing at?
You're holding it. The sword.
It's cold!
Want me to tell you why
you can't control time anymore?
You're probably thinking,
"God is disappointed in my worthless,
pathetic self," aren't ya?
Don't worry.
It's nothing as dramatic as that.
The reason you can't control time is simple.
It's because you've lost in your heart.
My heart?
Magic is a means to change the world.
You need three things to do that.
You need the magical power
to create change.
You need the process that gives
direction to that change.
And lastly, you need the confidence to control
the change once it's been actualized.
Y-you're saying it's a mental problem?
I bet every time you use magic,
the image of your enemy
surges through your mind, right?
That enemy could move even though
I made the world fall still!
Even though I did not give him
permission to move,
he attacked me while time was stopped!
I dunno why he didn't stop moving.
But the reason everything else won't stop
is because you've lost in your heart.
The Winged Monarch? What a laugh!
Right now, your heart is too beaten down
to rule over anything.
You're more like Traumatia now.
Traumatia?
What should I do?
What do I need to do to use
Time Control Magic again?
That's a piece of cake.
You gotta forget your fear.
Take that sword.
You were afraid of it at first,
but then you grabbed it without faltering
and cut me down.
For a second, you forgot your fear
because of the rage you felt towards me.
Forget my fear...
Forget my fear of the enemy...
Don't act like it's so easy!
If it was that straightforward,
I wouldn't be struggling like this!
Command me.
Command me to obliterate
the source of your fear,
and your fear will be a thing of the past.
Say it.
What do you want me to do?
No. I won't command you.
What?
Losing my Time Control Magic is simply
my own personal failure.
I can't use you, my greatest weapon,
to get my power back.
Right now, the top priority is
to annihilate this country
so the world can be shaped as God desires.
That is my sole duty as
the Winged Progenitor.
Well, I didn't want the answer
I should use to ace the test.
Tell me what you really want.
What you truly desire.
What?
What you really want me to do is...
get revenge, right?
Then how 'bout I tell you
what I really want first?
It enrages me that some bastard
tried to kill my woman while I was gone.
Since when did I become your woman!
How long will you insist on clowning around
and making a fool of me!
If you don't intend on listening to me,
go ahead and fight! That's fine by me!
I want to fight because you ordered me to.
I'm not gonna bow and scrape
because you're the progenitor
or worship you like some saint.
To me, you're just an unhinged woman.
An unhin-?
And I'm following this unhinged woman
of my own volition.
I don't give a rat's ass about God,
or allegiance to our blood,
or any of that garbage.
So you can act however you want around me.
You can piss and moan about your problems.
You can blow your top and bawl your eyes out.
You can be selfish like a child.
For you, I can take it all.
I'll always be by your side.
Th-there's no way
I can allow that for myself.
I have a duty to my God and bloodline.
And above all, I have a duty to the
immense number of people we've killed.
My personal desires-
And I don't doubt that those are
your true feelings.
But that's not what I'm trying to ask you.
Say it.
Tell me what you want me to do.
Bring... me...
their heads.
I actually said it.
Everything is their fault.
If it wasn't for them...
I'm sick of it...
I'm sick of it! I'm so sick of it!
I cannot bear it any longer!
Why is it that we're the only ones who suffer
while they get to continue living?
It's simply not fair!
This is an order, Woltekamui!
Kill them!
Use the full extent of your
phenomenal fighting prowess!
Rip off their heads and bring them to me!
Attagirl.
Leave it to me.
Your wish is my command.
Tia!
Lady Ultimatia!
I'm sorry, Tia!
I wasn't there when you really needed me.
No, I'm sorry for making you worry!
I'm okay now.
Oh, that's right! Nebulim!
Are you all right?
This oaf threatened you into letting him
into my chamber, didn't he?
The kiddo said it was totally cool
for me to go in. Right?
You liar!
It is true, Lady Ultimatia.
Nebulim would never disobey my orders.
I let Kamui walk right in.
He's a good boy, unlike you.
Given the state you were in,
You shouldn't set such high expectations
for kiddos, ya know?
I knew only Kamui's words
would get through to you.
You have some nerve trying to admonish me!
What can I do to get closer to
Lady Ultimatia's heart?
As close as he is to her...
What was that? Huh?
The Reaper...
will...
hunt you!
That guy really got my hopes up.
When was the last time I felt
this pumped to fight someone?
And an opponent I've never even seen!
When we finally face down, let's have a fight
to the death that'll go down in history!
Whaddaya think, Reaper?